primeloops.com 2012-06-06

# Prime Loops | Privacy Policy Page

1\. This Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat the personal information which you provide to us while using the website located at www.primeloops.com (the "Site") and/or the services provided from it (the "Services"). You are deemed to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy on your first use of the Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be effective from the date and time the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Site. The Site, together with all its content is owned or controlled by Sound Nation Limited, of Morrell Business Centre, 98 Curtain Road, London EC2A 3AF, United Kingdom.

2\. To provide the Site and the Services, it is necessary for us to hold and process certain personal information. We take reasonable care in keeping this information secure and preventing any unauthorised access or unlawful use of it. All personal information is processed by us in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.

3\. From time to time, we may collect or ask you to provide some or all of the following: name, address, date of birth, gender, music and/or software details and preferences, details of your music player devices, email addresses and/or mobile phone numbers, financial information such as credit/debit card numbers, IP addresses, web-browser details, operating system details, and/or your activities on the Site. This information will be stored together with any additional information you may provide to us from time to time, and will be used to provide you with the Services and services associated with them. We may also use your personal information:

  * to analyse use of the Site; and,
  * to keep you up-to-date with other products and services that we think may be of interest to you.

4\. We will only keep your personal information for as long as is necessary for the purposes for which that personal information was given to us. We may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by Users will, where relevant, be transferred and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you. In such event, you may not be contacted or informed of these changes.

5\. We may use 'cookies' while you access the Site to avoid the need to re-enter details on different occasions. If you do not wish to receive 'cookies', you may change the settings on your computer or browser accordingly.

6\. If you do not want us to retain or use your personal information in any way, please do not provide the data to us or, if you have already provided personal information and wish to withdraw your consent, please contact us at info@primeloops.com or by post at: Sound Nation Limited, of Morrell Business Centre, 98 Curtain Road, London EC2A 3AF, United Kingdom.

7\. If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted-out of receiving, please contact us at please contact us at info@primeloops.com or by post at: Sound Nation Limited, of Morrell Business Centre, 98 Curtain Road, London EC2A 3AF, United Kingdom.

© 2012 Prime Loops. All rights reserved.
